&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以，基本上就是优化-js试图找出做的方法
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So yeah, basically
optimize-js tries to figure out ways to do
本来会很懒的事情。
things that would have been lazy.
然后是急切解析，跳到急切解析，
And then eager parsed,
to just skip to the eager parsing,
因为做一次更快。
because doing it once is faster.
所以我们可以得到一些不同的图书馆，
So we can grab some different libraries,
拉入jQuery。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：和
pull in jQuery.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And
您可以看到，在没有优化的情况下，解析花费了16毫秒。
you can see that without optimize,
it took 16 milliseconds to parse.
使用优化，我们减少了一毫秒，或者说几乎减少了两毫秒。
With optimize, we shaved a millisecond
off, or almost two milliseconds off.
你可以抓取Lodash，同样是两毫秒。
You can grab Lodash,
again two milliseconds.
如果我们的目标是把所有东西都放在屏幕上，这是一个库，对吧？
And if we're aiming for getting everything
on the screen, this is one library, right?
继续前进可能真的很有用
It could be really useful to go ahead and
我们刮掉的每一毫秒都很重要。
every one of these milliseconds
that we shave off is important.
这甚至还不是我们的应用程序代码。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：ThreeJS
This is not even our application code yet.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: ThreeJS
是不是快了5毫秒，对吧？
is 5 milliseconds faster, right?
所以你说，是的，一直在用它，对吧？
So you were like, yeah,
use it all the time, right?
但这些都是人为的例子，对吧？
But these are, again,
contrived examples, right?
有人在其他浏览器上尝试过吗？
Did anyone try it in other browsers?
你的一些发现是什么？&gt；&gt；学生：Chrome的速度要快得多
What was some of your findings?
&gt;&gt; Student: Chrome is way faster with
jQuery而不是Firefox。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：是的，每个人都是
jQuery than Firefox.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah, each one is
以不同的方式实现，并且在那里做出了一些不同的决定。
implemented differently, and there's some
different decisions that are made there.
所以重要的是不要只测试Chrome，但是
And so it's important to not be
the person only testing Chrome, but
查看其他浏览器。
to look at other browsers as well.
因为这就是一些与测量有关的性能问题
Because this is where some of
the performance stuff with the measuring
变得极其重要。
becomes incredibly important.
所以如果我们拿一堆图书馆，我们运行它，
So if we take a bunch of libraries,
and we run it through,
我们可以在Chrome 55中看到这一点。
we can see that In Chrome 55.
一般来说，在大多数情况下都有明显的改善
Generally speaking there is
a noticeable improvement across most of
应用程序。
the applications.
你就像，运送它，是的，让我们把它放在我们的Webpack构建管道中。
You're like, ship it, yeah, let's put
it in our Webpack build pipeline.
一切都很好，这会很棒的，
Everything's great,
this is gonna be wonderful,
无处不在。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：但是
use it everywhere.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: But
跨库的故事在Edge 14上就不那么简单了，对吗？
the story across libraries is not as
straightforward on Edge 14, right?
我们可以看到，是的，ImmutableJS，有30%的改进，
We can see that, yeah, ImmutableJS,
there's a 30% improvement,
但是如果你使用的是PouchDB，那么它会慢32%，对吧？
but if you're using PouchDB,
well it's 32% slower, right?
如果我们只是遵循这些规则，把这些括号放在每个地方。
And if we just follow these rules,
put these parentheses everywhere.
您可能会使应用程序变慢。
You could be making applications slower.
您可以使应用程序更快，
You can be making applications faster,
这就是为什么测量非常重要。
so that's why it's really
important to measure.
如果我们看一下Safari，我们会得到一个略有不同的故事
We get a slightly different story if
we look in Safari where it's almost
普遍是个坏主意，[笑]对吧？
universally a bad idea, [LAUGH] right?
在大多数情况下，它会使事情变得更慢。
In most cases it is making stuff slower.
这归结到所有这些浏览器的实现细节，对吗？
That comes down to the implementation
details of all of these browsers, right?
所以再一次
And so again,
这个故事的寓意是确保你在测量，对吗？
the kind of moral of the story here is to
make sure that you're measuring, right?
并希望看到这些事情的实际影响和影响。
And looking to see what the actual impacts
and implications of these things are.
而不是仅仅遵循我告诉你的一些规则，或者
Rather than just following
some rule that I told you, or
一些类似的东西。
something along those lines.
用健康的怀疑态度对待我，并且
Treat me with a healthy
dose of skepticism, and
从我嘴里说出来的每一个字，对吗？
every word that's coming out of my mouth,
right?
[笑]把这些话拿来和你的申请做对比，
[LAUGH] Take those words,
measure them against your application,
那就做个决定。&gt；&gt；学生2：我可以问一个简短的问题吗？
then make a decision.
&gt;&gt; Student2: Can I ask a quick question?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：是的。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；学生2：当我们在做
&gt;&gt; Student2: When we're doing
函数声明并将它们包装在括号中。
function declarations and
wrapping them in parens.
如果你使用的是函数表达式，这会有什么不同吗？
If you're using a function expression
instead does that make a difference here?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：我认为，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: I think,
我保留在这件事上犯错的权利，但是
I reserve the right to
be wrong about this, but
我相信那些也是懒惰的部分。
I believe that those
are also still lazy parts.
但是IFFE，例如那些立即调用的函数表达式，
But IFFEs, for instance, those
immediately invoked function expressions,
我们将它们放在括号中，并立即调用它们。
we wrap them in the parentheses,
and immediately call them.
例如，这些都是开箱即用的急切解析，对吧？
Those, for instance, are eagerly
parsed right out of the box, right?
所以有不同的用例，还有另一种
So there is different use cases,
and the other kind of again
我现在要做的免责声明是很多这些规则的改变，对吗？
disclaimer that I'm gonna make now is
a lot of these rules change, right?
Chrome团队正在努力让这个东西变得更好，对吗？
The Chrome team is working on
making this stuff better, right?
这就是为什么要及早测量，经常测量，对吧？
Which is why measure early,
measure often, right?
当我们到达实际的编译引擎和
When we get to the actual
compiling engine and
它所做的优化，对吧？
the optimizations that it makes, right?
那是一个移动的目标，对，现在有些东西很慢，
That's a moving target, right,
there are things that are slow now,
当ES6最初问世的时候。
when ES6 originally came out.
所有用于浏览器的ES6内容都比ES5内容慢。
All of the ES6 stuff that was for
the browser was slower than the ES5 stuff.
所以很容易，读一篇博客文章，然后
So it would be very easy to
,read a blog post then and
相信ES6天生就比较慢。
believe that ES6 was inherently slower.
它之所以慢，是因为浏览器发明者有十年的时间来优化。
It was slower because browser
inventors had ten years to optimize.
并找出ES5材料的所有边缘情况
And figure out all the edge cases for
the ES5 stuff and
ES6的东西是全新的，对吧？
the ES6 stuff was brand new, right?
三年后，这不再是真的了，对吗？
Three years later,
that is not true anymore right?
因为浏览器供应商正在尝试改进和
Because the browser vendors
are attempting to get better and
用这些东西更快。
faster with these things.
所以一般来说，所有这些东西都是一个移动的目标。
So generally speaking,
all these things are a moving target.
这就是为什么我一直说，在每张幻灯片之间测量几乎是一个节拍。
And that's why I keep saying measure
almost a beat in between every slide.
如果你真的想用这个，如果你的研究进展顺利。
If you did want to use this,
if your research goes well.
您可以看到，您在各个方面都获得了性能提升。
And you can see that you have
performance gains across the board.
还有Webpack插件，
There are also Webpack plugins,
我们也可以将这个插入到您的构建管道中。
we can just insert this into
your build pipeline as well.
只是一些其他的快速，
Just some other quick,
关于解析的可口笔记。&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：只要我们有
tasty notes on parsing.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Whenever we have
位于另一个函数内部的函数，
a function that is inside
of another function,
有效地总是被懒惰地解析，对吗？
that is effectively always going
to be lazily parsed, right?
所以如果我们把它移出，它可以在一个单独的拍摄中被解析，
So if we move that out, it can get
parsed in a separate take on it,
在这种情况下，它将获得更好的性能，对吗？
in this case it will get
better performance right?
你可以争辩这是不是意味着，让我们休息15分钟，
You can argue does that mean,
let's take a 15 minute break,
你遍历了巨大的代码库并重构了所有东西吗？
you go through your giant code base and
refactor everything?
可能不是，有一些工具可以帮助你，
Probably not, there are tools
that can help you with this,
我们将在最后讨论，但同样，只是一些需要考虑的东西。
that we'll cover at the end, but again,
just something to kinda think about.